<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Juan Andrés Nin</title>
    <link>http://www.nin.com.uy/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Juan Andrés Nin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://www.nin.com.uy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Going indie in 2022</title>
      <link>http://www.nin.com.uy/posts/indie-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.nin.com.uy/posts/indie-2022/</guid>
      <description>Since the beginning of 2022 I&amp;rsquo;ve been working full time as an indie game developer. First of all, some background on myself.
The past 30th of December was my last day as a developer at Ironhide Game Studio. Almost ten years working on great games like the Kingdom Rush series, learning a lot not only as a programmer but in all areas of game development. Alongside Manuel we founded Tragico Media and are currently working on our first game Tourist Trap, a dark comedy point and click adventure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://www.nin.com.uy/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.nin.com.uy/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m Juan Andrés Nin a programmer and game designer from Uruguay with more than 10 years of professional experience.
In 2021 I cofounded Tragico Media where we are currently working on our first game: a surrealist comedy point and click adventure.
Previously I worked at Ironhide Game Studio.
I have worked on the following games:
Junkworld
Worked as lead programmer on multiple prototypes during preproduction and led a team of three programmers from this stage onto softlaunch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First post</title>
      <link>http://www.nin.com.uy/posts/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.nin.com.uy/posts/first-post/</guid>
      <description>This is a first post on a blog which hopefully sees new content in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://www.nin.com.uy/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.nin.com.uy/contact/</guid>
      <description>You can find me on twitter or contact me by email.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
